【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 3]
[3화]
Master, are you okay?
선생님, 괜찮으세요?
Master.
주인.
I'm fine.
잘 지내요.
How is she today?
오늘 그녀는 어때요?
she's fine. Miss He and He San went to the horse market together.
그녀는 괜찮아. Miss He 와 He San은 함께 말 시장에 갔습니다.
General He has just arrived at the mansion.
장군 그는 방금 저택에 도착했습니다.
He brought several Turkish horses with him.
그는 여러 마리의 터키 말을 데리고 왔습니다.
It must be a gift from the lady. Hey.
분명 아줌마가 준 선물이겠지. 여기요.
She sends a letter every day.
그녀는 매일 편지를 보낸다.
She is always thinking of you.
그녀는 항상 당신을 생각하고 있습니다.
I'm going to visit the General's Mansion.
장군 저택을 방문할 예정입니다.
it's getting dark.
어두워지고있다.
Now is not a good time.
지금은 좋은 때가 아니다.
Master, why don't you wait until tomorrow?
선생님, 내일까지 기다리시는 게 어때요?
When Miss He sends me a letter tomorrow ,
Miss He가 내일 나에게 편지를 보내면 ,
You can simply respond.
간단하게 응답하시면 됩니다.
if we leave now
우리 지금 떠나면
Maybe we can't see it.
어쩌면 우리는 그것을 볼 수 없습니다.
It's not that I want to see her.
내가 그녀를 보고 싶은 것은 아니다.
I just wanted to be close to her.
나는 단지 그녀와 가까워지고 싶었습니다.
Even just a little closer.
조금만 더 가까이 있어도 말이죠.
enough.
충분한.
I can't believe you're laughing at me.
당신이 나를 비웃는 걸 믿을 수가 없어요.
Master taught me a lot.
스승님은 나에게 많은 것을 가르쳐 주셨습니다.
I can't even cancel the wedding.
결혼식도 취소 못해요.
If you want to apply what the teacher taught you,
선생님께서 가르쳐주신 내용을 적용하고 싶다면,
I should kill Rong Yu.
나는 Rong Yu를 죽여야한다.
How can you say that?
어떻게 그런 말을 할 수가있어?
How can you take it seriously?
어떻게 진지하게 받아들일 수 있나요?
I was joking.
농담 이었어.
It's not funny.
그것은 재미 없어.
I really miss my days in Wuhuashan.
저는 Wuhuashan에서의 시절이 정말 그리워요.
At that time, you always cooked terrible meals for me.
그 당시 당신은 항상 나를 위해 끔찍한 음식을 요리해 주었습니다.
When the master taught me how to make medicine,
스승님께서 나에게 약 만드는 법을 가르쳐 주실 때,
He always comes up with weird ways to torture me.
그는 항상 나를 고문하기 위해 이상한 방법을 생각해냅니다 .
And I deal with scorpions and centipedes every day.
그리고 저는 매일 전갈과 지네를 다루고 있습니다.
but i have nothing
하지만 난 아무것도 없어
how to worry
걱정하는 방법
I thought it was simple.
나는 그것이 간단하다고 생각했다.
Quando chegou ao Monte Wuhua,
Quando chegou ao Monte Wuhua,
She is as sick as an old woman.
그녀는 노파만큼 아프다.
You always say you want to go up the mountain and catch birds.
당신은 항상 산에 올라가서 새를 잡고 싶다고 말해요 .
Or jump into the river and fish.
아니면 강에 뛰어들어 낚시를 해보세요.
Whenever I let my guard down, you disappear.
내가 방심할 때마다 당신은 사라져요.
you make me so angry
넌 날 너무 화나게 만들어
Who wants to tie you up with a rope.
누가 당신을 밧줄로 묶고 싶어 할까요?
When you recover, you become even more shameful.
회복되면 더욱 부끄러워집니다.
You said Master was playing tricks on you.
당신은 스승님이 당신을 속이고 있다고 말했습니다 .
Have you forgotten how you played a trick on your master?
당신이 당신의 주인에게 어떻게 장난을 쳤는지 잊었나요?
So, it’s not like I haven’t had problems.
그러니 나에게 문제가 없었던 것은 아니다.
But he hasn't found them yet.
하지만 그는 아직 그것들을 찾지 못했습니다.
Only children have no problem.
아이들만 문제 없습니다.
I promise you that in a few years you will be living a peaceful life.
나는 몇 년 안에 당신이 평화로운 삶을 살 것이라고 약속합니다.
Don't say stupid things.
어리석은 말을하지 마십시오.
Keep in touch with me and the master.
저와 마스터에게 계속 연락하세요.
After you left Wuhuashan a few years ago,
몇 년 전 당신이 Wuhuashan을 떠난 후,
and travel around the world,
그리고 전 세계를 여행하고,
Master and I almost turned into stone waiting for you.
스승님과 나는 당신을 기다리며 돌이 될 뻔했습니다.
We want to send a letter but don't know where to send it.
편지를 보내고 싶은데 어디로 보내야 할지 모르겠어요.
I had no one to talk to when I felt wronged .
내가 부당하다고 느꼈을 때 이야기할 사람이 없었습니다 .
These few years.
이 몇 년.
Ling, no matter what happens,
링, 무슨 일이 있어도
You will always be my most beloved sister.
당신은 항상 내가 가장 사랑하는 여동생이 될 것입니다 .
This won't happen again.
이런 일은 다시는 일어나지 않을 것입니다.
If you feel aggrieved
불만을 느끼면
Please let me help.
도와주세요.
Could it be?
그럴 수 있을까?
why not?
왜 안 돼?
Use your wisdom,
당신의 지혜를 활용하세요.
Every problem can be solved.
모든 문제는 해결될 수 있습니다.
【Master Zhirong】
【지롱대사】
Unconditional kindness is to satisfy evil.
무조건적인 친절은 악을 만족시키는 것입니다.
Does he like me?
그 사람이 나를 좋아하나요?
If you feel you've been cheated,
속았다고 느끼면,
let me help you. he can?
내가 도와 줄게. 그는 할 수있다?
Why don't I let it?
내가 허락하지 않는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Use your wisdom,
당신의 지혜를 활용하세요.
Every problem can be solved.
모든 문제는 해결될 수 있습니다.
What if they propose to you?
그들이 당신에게 프로포즈한다면 어떨까요?
Isn't it just jumping from one hell to another?
그것은 단지 한 지옥에서 다른 지옥으로 점프하는 것이 아닌가 ?
You have to marry someone you know.
아는 사람과 결혼해야 해요.
Someone with whom they have a mutual understanding, right?
서로 이해가 되는 사람이겠죠?
What if that person is me?
그 사람이 나라면 어떡하지?
Don't wait.
기다리지 마세요.
He said it was only a matter of time.
그는 시간문제일 뿐이라고 말했습니다.
We'll talk after I cancel the wedding.
내가 결혼식을 취소한 후에 얘기하자.
I'd better get engaged to him first.
먼저 그 사람과 약혼하는 게 좋겠어요.
It would be great if it were him.
그 사람이라면 정말 좋을 것 같아요.
Big brother is very good to me. He has superb martial arts skills.
큰 형은 나에게 아주 좋은 사람이에요. 그는 뛰어난 무술 실력을 가지고 있습니다.
Everything about it is good.
그것에 관한 모든 것이 좋습니다.
I'd better lie to my brother to get married.
결혼하려면 동생 에게 거짓말을 하는 게 낫겠어요 .
why not?
왜 안 돼?
I'm really a bad girl!
난 정말 나쁜 여자야!
Rong Yu, you idiot.
롱유, 이 바보야.
You ruined my relationship with my brother.
당신은 내 동생과의 관계를 망쳤습니다.
If my sister were here
내 여동생이 여기 있었다면
Will she help me?
그녀가 나를 도와줄까?
Young boss.
젊은 상사.
miss. He looked drunk.
놓치다. 그는 취한 것처럼 보였다.
go.
가다.
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
I'll call you
내가 전화할게
With my thoughts?
내 생각으로?
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
Do you want to run away again?
또 도망가고 싶니?
SEM opportunities.
SEM 기회.
She bullied him again
그 사람이 또 그 사람을 괴롭혔어요
I need to save it.
저장해야 해요.
you.
너.
Don't think you can escape.
탈출할 수 있을 거라 생각하지 마세요.
Ms. He.
그 씨.
European Union...
유럽 ​​연합...
I won't run away. I just don't think we should touch each other.
나는 도망치지 않을 것이다. 내 생각엔 우리가 서로 만지면 안 될 것 같아.
You are afraid of me.
당신은 나를 두려워합니다.
No.
아니요.
Do not move.
이동하지 않습니다.
Didn't I convince her enough?
내가 그녀를 충분히 설득하지 않았나요?
I've never been so patient with anyone.
나는 누구에게도 그렇게 인내심을 가져본 적이 없습니다.
Since childhood.
어린 시절부터.
Why didn't you show up when I asked?
내가 물었을 때 왜 나타나지 않았나요?
You know we need to talk.
우리 얘기 좀 해야 한다는 거 알잖아요.
you think
당신 생각에는
Call me a devil?
날 악마라고 불러?
That's my fault.
내 탓이야.
It's your fault.
그건 당신 잘못이에요.
You're making things complicated now.
당신은 지금 일을 복잡하게 만들고 있습니다.
Why do you want to propose to me so badly?
왜 나에게 그렇게 심하게 프러포즈하려는 거야?
And then blame me for it.
그리고 그것에 대해 나를 비난하십시오.
I didn't say that.
나는 그렇게 말하지 않았다.
How could you say such a thing in front of Master Rong?
어떻게 롱 선생님 앞에서 그런 말을 할 수 있었나요?
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I should say that's my wish.
그게 내 소원이라고 해야 할까 .
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
If you want to be happy,
행복 해지고 싶다면,
You shouldn't take commitments so seriously.
약속을 그렇게 심각하게 받아들여서는 안 됩니다.
I'm not a good woman.
나는 좋은 여자가 아니다.
I don't know how to play an instrument. I don't know how to memorize poetry.
나는 악기를 연주하는 방법을 모른다. 나는 시를 어떻게 외우는지 모른다.
I don't know how to help my husband or teach my children.
남편을 어떻게 도와야 할지 , 아이들을 가르쳐야 할지 모르겠습니다 .
I couldn’t even make my own wedding dress.
웨딩드레스를 직접 만들 수도 없었어요.
if i get married
내가 결혼하면
With a 50-year-old widower,
50세 홀아비와 함께
I won't be happy.
나는 행복하지 않을 것이다.
You must be feeling terrible, right?
기분이 정말 끔찍할 것 같죠?
look at your face.
얼굴 좀 봐.
Miss He, please don’t!
Miss He, 제발 그러지 마세요!
Please don't touch me again.
다시는 나를 만지지 마세요.
look at your face. You never dared to look me in the eye.
얼굴 좀 봐. 당신은 감히 내 눈을 똑바로 쳐다보지 못했습니다.
You have a bride like me.
당신에겐 나 같은 신부가 있어요.
What a shame.
정말 부끄러운 일입니다.
to be honest.
솔직히 말하자면.
you do not like me. It's because you're afraid of me.
넌 날 좋아하지 않아. 당신이 나를 두려워하기 때문이에요.
It is not?
그렇지 않습니까?
It is not? reply.
그렇지 않습니까? 회신하다.
I do not want.
하고 싶지 않다.
You are a nerd.
당신은 괴짜입니다.
Everyone says you respect promises and rituals.
모두가 당신이 약속과 의식을 존중한다고 말합니다 .
But I think you're just being stubborn.
하지만 내 생각엔 당신이 고집을 부리는 것뿐인 것 같아요.
looking at you.
너를보고있는.
What can I expect from someone like you?
당신 같은 사람에게 내가 무엇을 기대할 수 있습니까?
but i can't say
하지만 난 말할 수 없어
In a place like this.
이런 곳에서.
I hate how boring this is.
나는 이것이 얼마나 지루한지 싫어한다.
You, an adult, cannot
어른인 당신은 할 수 없습니다
Is it direct and correct?
직접적이고 정확합니까?
do not be afraid.
두려워 하지마.
Did I scare you?
내가 널 겁 줬니?
Let me comfort you.
내가 당신을 위로하자.
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
if you could stand up straight
똑바로 설 수 있다면
I said.
나는 말했다.
Of course I can.
당연히 할 수있다.
European Union...
유럽 ​​연합...
they say you are
그들은 당신이 그렇다고 말해요
Expressive and talented.
표현력이 뛰어나고 재능이 있습니다.
He is the best young master in Jialin.
그는 Jialin 최고의 젊은 스승입니다.
But you stumble over your words.
그러나 당신은 당신의 말에 걸려 넘어졌습니다.
How can a person be eloquent?
사람이 어떻게 말을 잘할 수 있나요?
In front of someone you like?
좋아하는 사람 앞에서?
like?
좋다?
i liked you
내가 당신을 좋아
long time.
장기.
Take back what you said before speaking again.
다시 말하기 전에 말한 내용을 취소하세요.
I'll give you another chance.
또 다른 기회를 드리겠습니다.
I don't give everyone a second chance.
나는 모든 사람에게 두 번째 기회를 주지 않습니다.
Take your time.
천천히하세요.
Think before you speak and speak well.
말하기 전에 생각하고 잘 말하십시오.
About our engagement,
우리의 약혼에 대해,
I'm very happy.
나는 매우 행복 해요.
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
Go away, devil.
가버려, 악마야.
disappear!
사라지다!
He is still laughing. I'm sad that he's still laughing.
그는 아직도 웃고 있다. 그 사람이 아직도 웃고 있어서 안타깝다 .
If I were to marry a psychic
만약 내가 심령술사와 결혼한다면
generate some spirituality
영성을 생성하다
And spend my life witnessing them both
그리고 그 둘을 목격하며 평생을 보내죠
Burning turtle shells or counting stars,
거북이 껍질을 태우거나 별을 세거나,
I'd rather die.
차라리 죽고 싶습니다.
In fact, it would be great if our son were a general.
사실 우리 아들이 장군이었다면 정말 좋았을 텐데요.
Future general.
미래 장군.
He is your little general Rong.
그는 당신의 작은 장군 롱입니다.
What if it's a girl?
여자라면 어떡하지?
So love her as much as you can.
그러니 최대한 그녀를 사랑하세요.
We won't let her go for a day
우리는 그녀를 하루 동안 보내지 않을 것입니다
Ten is much less.
10은 훨씬 적습니다.
I will never let her face the ordeal of Mount Wuhua.
나는 결코 그녀가 우화산의 시련을 겪게 하지 않을 것이다 .
Maybe I'm late.
어쩌면 내가 늦었을지도 몰라.
But I promise you won't suffer anymore.
하지만 더 이상 고통받지 않겠다고 약속합니다.
I will always protect you.
나는 항상 당신을 보호할 것입니다.
I promise.
약속해요.
you?
너?
One poke can knock you out.
한 번 찌르면 쓰러질 수 있습니다.
You don’t even know how to ride a horse.
당신은 말을 타는 법도 모릅니다.
How dare you promise me? What will you get for me?
어떻게 감히 나에게 약속해? 나에게 무엇을 주실 건가요?
He just said he wanted to have a baby with me.
그는 방금 나와 함께 아기를 갖고 싶다고 말했습니다.
I do not want.
하고 싶지 않다.
Yes.
예.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
General Rong? To love her as much as we can?
롱 장군? 그녀를 최대한 사랑하기 위해?
what is that?
저게 뭐에요?
As the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion,
Xingxiang Pavilion의 젊은 스승으로서,
You don't acknowledge what you said.
당신은 당신이 말한 것을 인정하지 않습니다.
I warn you.
경고합니다.
Not only can't I think about it,
생각도 못 할 뿐만 아니라,
You can't even like me.
당신은 나를 좋아할 수도 없습니다.
Silta. he. Silta. he.
실타. 그. 실타. 그.
Master. I'm late.
주인. 나는 늦었다.
It was Heshan who wouldn't let me come.
내가 오지 못하게 한 사람은 허샨이었습니다.
If a lady he insults you drunk
여자가 술에 취해 너를 모욕 하면
I will never forgive myself.
나는 결코 나 자신을 용서하지 않을 것입니다.
She won't hurt me.
그녀는 나를 해치지 않을 것입니다.
Flatten, don't worry.
평평하게 하세요. 걱정하지 마세요.
Not the future,
미래가 아닌,
Even if she abuses me, please leave her.
그녀가 나를 학대하더라도 떠나주세요.
Is this poisoning?
이거 중독인가요?
certainly.
틀림없이.
Just a little narcotic.
약간의 마약이군요.
Heshan, please ask Mr. He to take her back.
허산 씨, 허 씨에게 그녀를 다시 데려가달라고 부탁하세요.
I can't take her inside.
나는 그녀를 안으로 데려갈 수 없습니다.
When the servants saw it, they started talking about it.
하인들이 그것을 보고 그것에 대해 이야기하기 시작했습니다.
Sim.
심.
teacher.
선생님.
Master Rong sent a message
Master Rong이 메시지를 보냈습니다.
Miss He was accidentally injured and fainted.
Miss 그는 실수로 부상을 입고 기절했습니다.
He wants you to bring her back.
그는 당신이 그녀를 다시 데려오길 원합니다.
How did she get injured? Is it serious? Where is she?
그녀는 어떻게 부상을 입었나요? 심각합니까? 그녀는 어디 있습니까?
Although it was a dart injury, it was not serious.
다트 부상이었지만 심각하지는 않았다.
Now, she is in the carriage in front of our house.
지금 그 사람은 우리 집 앞 마차에 타고 있어요.
ah
아
Is Mr. Rong taking care of her?
롱씨가 그녀를 돌보고 있나요?
Sim.
심.
Then reply to him.
그런 다음 그에게 답장하십시오.
The person who caused the harm must be held accountable.
피해를 준 사람은 책임을 져야 합니다.
Fortunately he continued to take care of her.
다행히 그는 계속해서 그녀를 돌보았습니다.
OK...
좋아요...
You can go.
당신은 갈 수 있습니다.
Sim.
심.
Don't you want to bring Ling back?
링을 다시 데려오고 싶지 않나요?
Master Rong and her
롱 선생님과 그녀
They are not married yet.
그들은 아직 결혼하지 않았습니다.
if she was with someone else
그 사람이 다른 사람이랑 같이 있었다면
I will definitely bring her back.
나는 반드시 그녀를 다시 데려올 것이다.
But she was with Master Rong.
하지만 그녀는 Rong 선생님과 함께 있었어요.
I'm sure she's fine.
그녀는 괜찮을 거라고 확신해요.
also,
또한,
I hope Ling can spend more time with Rong Yu.
Ling이 Rong Yu와 더 많은 시간을 보낼 수 있기를 바랍니다 .
let's go.
갑시다.
【He is a mansion】
【그는 저택이다】
Master, shall we go back now?
선생님 이제 돌아갈까요?
Let's go to the courtyard.
안뜰로 가자.
Heshan, you go first.
허샨, 먼저 가세요.
Remember to fire all servants.
모든 하인을 해고하는 것을 잊지 마십시오.
Only one maid remained.
하녀 한 명만 남았습니다.
Sim.
심.
Master, come in quickly.
선생님, 빨리 들어오세요.
Can't stay here all night
여기서 밤새도록 있을 수는 없어
to avoid gossip.
험담을 피하기 위해.
Master, this is what Miss He dropped.
스승님, 이것이 Miss He가 떨어뜨린 것입니다.
Master, I don't want to complain.
선생님, 저는 불평하고 싶지 않습니다.
She is dishonest.
그녀는 부정직합니다.
He swore he was burned
그는 화상을 입었다고 맹세했어요
Astrology Festival Agenda.
점성술 축제 일정.
But it turns out it wasn't her.
그러나 그것은 그녀가 아니었다는 것이 밝혀졌습니다.
If I hadn't found him loose
내가 그 사람이 풀려난 걸 발견 하지 못했다면
I won't find out.
나는 알아 내지 않을 것이다.
Miss He actually wants
Miss 그는 실제로 원합니다
The paintings were secretly printed into prints.
그림은 비밀리 에 인쇄물로 인쇄되었습니다.
And keep them forever.
그리고 그것들을 영원히 간직하세요.
he's good.
그는 좋아.
save.
구하다.
Delete and destroy later.
나중에 삭제하고 파기하세요.
But what do we say to women? Well later?
하지만 우리는 여성들에게 무엇을 말합니까? 그럼 나중에?
Let's pretend we don't know.
우리가 모르는 척하자.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
Rong Yu!
유롱!
【He is a mansion】
【그는 저택이다】
General He,
그 장군님,
Congratulations on your promotion to first-level general.
1급 장군으로 진급하신 것을 축하드립니다 .
This is a gift from the emperor.
이것은 황제의 선물입니다.
I brought it myself.
제가 직접 가져왔습니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
should ask others
다른 사람한테 물어봐야지
Perform this small task.
이 작은 작업을 수행하십시오.
You shouldn't bother coming
귀찮게 오지 않아도 돼
too early.
너무 이른.
And how to express the emperor's favor?
그리고 황제의 호의를 어떻게 표현해야 할까요?
The emperor mentioned his daughter
황제는 자신의 딸을 언급했다
He left his hometown for ten years and only recently returned.
그는 10년 동안 고향을 떠났다가 최근에야 돌아왔다.
She must not have any aristocratic friends in the capital .
그녀는 수도에 귀족 친구가 없어야 합니다 .
For today’s banquet, Xunnan envoy,
오늘 연회를 위해 Xunnan 특사,
You need to take her with you.
그녀를 데리고 가야 해요.
Maybe she could make friends.
어쩌면 그녀는 친구를 사귈 수도 있을 것입니다.
return?
반품?
she...
그녀...
General He.
장군 그.
Is there anything inappropriate?
부적절한 것이 있나요?
never.
절대.
I express my highest gratitude to His Majesty.
폐하께 깊은 감사를 드립니다.
About our engagement,
우리의 약혼에 대해,
I'm very happy.
나는 매우 행복 해요.
Maybe I'm late,
어쩌면 내가 늦었을지도 모르지
But I promise you won't suffer anymore.
하지만 더 이상 고통받지 않겠다고 약속합니다.
I will always protect you.
나는 항상 당신을 보호할 것입니다.
I promise.
약속해요.
Azar.
아자르.
Master.
주인.
some problems?
몇 가지 문제?
Don't worry. Just saying.
괜찮아요. 그냥 말하는 거야.
Miss He got up very early
Miss 그는 아주 일찍 일어났어요
She was very angry.
그녀는 매우 화가났습니다.
As she left the courtyard, she kicked open the door.
그녀는 안뜰을 떠나면서 문을 발로 차서 열었습니다.
Even the stone lion at the door broke its head.
문 앞에 있던 돌사자마저도 머리가 부러졌습니다.
Many people here know
여기 많은 사람들이 알고 있어요
She spent the night in the yard.
그녀는 마당에서 밤을 보냈습니다.
Is she hurt?
그녀가 다쳤나요?
No, but...
아니, 하지만...
When she broke in she was wearing only her nightgown.
그녀가 침입했을 때 그녀는 잠옷만 입고 있었습니다.
Rumors may soon spread throughout the capital.
곧 수도 전역에 소문이 퍼질 수도 있습니다 .
This is difficult to understand.
이것은 이해하기 어렵습니다.
all good.
문제 없다.
I see.
알겠어요.
Wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
Send a letter to the general's residence.
장군의 거주지로 편지를 보내십시오.
How many times have I said
내가 몇 번이나 말했지?
There will be no result between Rong Yu and me.
Rong Yu와 나 사이에는 결과가 없을 것입니다.
- You - If you don't help me, someone else will.
- 당신 - 당신이 나를 돕지 않으면 다른 사람이 도와줄 거예요.
I didn't say that.
나는 그렇게 말하지 않았다.
Ling, go wash up and get dressed.
링, 가서 씻고 옷 입으세요.
I'll take you to the palace.
내가 당신을 궁전으로 데려갈게요.
General, the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion has sent news.
장군님, 흥향각의 젊은 스승께서 소식을 보내왔습니다.
They said it was important.
그들은 그것이 중요하다고 말했습니다.
[To General He] This is a letter from our young master.
[그 장군에게] 이것은 우리 젊은 스승님이 보내신 편지입니다.
please read.
읽어주세요.
Ling,
링,
There are many rules in the palace.
궁전에는 많은 규칙이 있습니다.
Try walking upright.
똑바로 걸어보세요.
Place your hands in front of you.
손을 앞에 놓으십시오.
Don't look around, okay?
주위를 둘러보지 마세요, 알았죠?
say what needs to be said
말해야 할 것을 말하다
And don't say things you shouldn't say.
그리고 해서는 안 될 말은 하지 마세요.
I'm going to see the queen.
여왕님을 만나러 가겠습니다.
Ling, the palace doesn't feel like home.
링, 궁전은 집처럼 느껴지지 않아요.
Proceed with caution.
조심해서 진행해라.
There is no one to protect her when we are not around.
우리가 없을 때 그녀를 보호해 줄 사람은 아무도 없습니다.
I see.
알겠어요.
Ling,
링,
Have you forgotten what I taught you?
내가 가르쳐준 걸 잊었나요?
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
let's go.
갑시다.
correct.
옳은.
again.
다시.
- Your Highness.
- 전하.
Cheng'an!
청안!
Chengan, are you okay?
청간아, 괜찮아?
Be bold! How dare you hurt the prince?
대담해지세요! 어떻게 감히 왕자님을 다치게 합니까?
Playing badminton is the same as taking turns.
배드민턴을 하는 것은 교대로 하는 것과 같습니다.
I'm kidding Your Highness.
농담입니다.
how dare you?
어떻게 감히?
The prince didn't say he wanted to play with you.
왕자님은 너랑 놀고 싶다고 말하지 않았어 .
all good. Actually I think
문제 없다. 사실 제 생각에는
You played shuttlecock very well.
셔틀콕을 아주 잘 치셨네요.
must. My brother He Qingxing plays better than me.
해야 하다. 내 동생 허칭싱(He Qingxing)이 나보다 플레이를 더 잘한다.
My name is He Jiuling.
내 이름은 He Jiuling입니다.
It turns out that you are the daughter that He Liang sent to Wuhua Mountain to study art.
알고 보니 당신은 허량이 미술을 공부하기 위해 우화산으로 보낸 딸이었습니다.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Sim.
심.
Hello, Your Majesty.
안녕하세요, 폐하.
Princess. Crown Prince.
공주. 왕세자.
Come and sit down.
와서 앉으세요.
Dad said there are many centipedes and scorpions on Wuhua Mountain.
아빠는 우화산(Wuhua Mountain)에 지네와 전갈이 많다고 하더군요.
I'm curious.
궁금해.
Miss He, what did you learn there?
Miss He, 거기서 무엇을 배웠나요?
How about it?
어때요?
I want to know what you learned in Wuhua Mountain.
나는 당신이 Wuhua Mountain에서 무엇을 배웠는지 알고 싶습니다.
What did it give me?
그것은 나에게 무엇을 주었나요?
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Your Majesty, please do not panic.
폐하, 당황하지 마십시오.
It's hard to explain in a few words what I learned.
내가 배운 것을 몇 마디 말로 설명하기 는 어렵다 .
Since Ms. Jiang is very curious,
Jiang 씨는 호기심이 많기 때문에
I think it's better for her to go through this on her own.
내 생각에는 그녀가 이 문제를 스스로 해결하는 것이 더 낫다고 생각합니다.
My master taught me how to make medicine.
나의 주인은 나에게 약 만드는 법을 가르쳐 주었습니다.
my best person
내 최고의 사람
It's deodorant pills.
데오드란트 알약이에요.
When you take medicine,
약을 먹으면,
Its body exudes a light fragrance.
몸에서는 가벼운 향기가 납니다.
She is harmless.
그녀는 무해합니다.
Even so,
비록 그렇다 하더라도,
You are too reckless.
당신은 너무 무모해요.
It's really my fault.
정말 내 잘못이에요.
It's interesting.
흥미 롭군.
When will I be able to smell this faint scent?
언제쯤이면 이 은은한 향기를 맡을 수 있을까요?
logo.
심벌 마크.
Why give me such a good thing?
왜 나한테 이런 좋은 걸 줘?
Instead of eating it yourself?
직접 먹는 것보다?
Peachy. It's a peach.
복숭아 같은. 복숭아예요.
The Crown Prince is my soul mate.
왕세자는 나의 소울메이트입니다.
The first aroma is peach and the last aroma is citrus.
첫 향은 복숭아 향이고 마지막 향은 시트러스 향이에요.
The fragrance remains for three days.
향은 3일간 지속됩니다.
I will withdraw.
철회하겠습니다.
How dare you taint my cousin.
감히 내 사촌을 더럽히다니.
He Jiuling, you have gone too far.
He Jiuling, 당신은 너무 멀리갔습니다.
Mom, you should punish her.
엄마, 그 사람을 처벌하셔야 해요.
Why punish her? She did nothing wrong.
왜 그녀를 처벌합니까? 그녀는 아무 잘못도 하지 않았습니다.
Curious was our cousin.
우리 사촌이 궁금했습니다.
Acho que a He Jiuling
Acho que a He Jiuling
Interesting.
흥미로운.
I like her. I want to play with her.
나는 그녀가 좋아. 나는 그녀와 놀고 싶다.
Let her come to the palace every day.
그녀가 매일 궁전에 오도록 해주세요.
Your Majesty,
폐하,
The emperor asked the lord and the prince,
황제가 영주 와 왕자에게 물었다.
And other maids in the palace also came to the banquet.
그리고 궁궐의 다른 시녀들도 잔치에 왔습니다.
affim. Apparently.
확증하다. 확실히.
Jiuling, when you see the emperor,
구릉이여, 황제를 보면
One should not be reckless.
무모해서는 안됩니다.
Otherwise, even I can't protect her.
그렇지 않으면 나조차도 그녀를 보호할 수 없다.
Sim.
심.
The queen is coming.
여왕이 온다.
Where is the pine forest?
소나무 숲은 어디에 있나요?
Why hasn't Pine Forest come yet?
소나무숲은 왜 아직 안오나요?
Tio,
티오,
My cousin was frightened by General He's daughter.
내 사촌은 장군의 딸 때문에 겁을 먹었습니다.
What's there?
거기 무엇이 있나요?
My mom told me not to tell.
엄마는 말하지 말라고 했어요.
I will tell.
나는 말할 것이다.
He Jiuling gave my cousin a pill
He Jiuling은 내 사촌에게 약을 주었다
It can make people 's bodies smell good.
그것은 사람들 의 몸에서 좋은 냄새를 풍길 수 있습니다.
Until my cousin got angry.
내 사촌이 화를 낼 때까지.
Dad, she's so funny.
아빠, 그 사람 정말 재밌어요.
Can I invite her to play with me more in the future?
앞으로 그녀를 더 많이 나와 함께 놀도록 초대해도 될까요 ?
What might the aromatic smell be?
향기로운 냄새는 무엇일까요?
Why does this anger her?
이것이 왜 그녀를 화나게 하는가?
This is because...
이 때문입니다...
Cheng'an
청안
I don't know either.
나도 모른다.
Your Majesty,
폐하,
My daughter grew up in the mountains and doesn’t understand etiquette.
내 딸은 산에서 자랐기 때문에 예절을 이해하지 못합니다.
If she offends someone,
그녀가 누군가에게 불쾌감을 준다면,
I am willing to accept punishment.
나는 처벌을 기꺼이 받아들인다.
my Lord,
군주,
I'm very sorry.
나는 매우 미안 해요.
General He, how polite!
그 장군님, 얼마나 예의바른지요!
please sit down.
앉으세요.
General He's daughter is deeply favored by the prince.
장군의 딸은 왕자의 총애를 받고 있다.
The most annoying one is Princess Jialin.
가장 짜증나는 사람은 Jialin 공주입니다.
She must be interesting.
그녀는 흥미로울 것 같아요.
What we are discussing today is
오늘 우리가 논의할 내용은
Jialin formed an alliance with Xunnan.
Jialin은 Xunnan과 동맹을 맺었습니다.
I think it’s better for a woman to marry Xunnan
여자가 쑨난과 결혼하는 게 더 낫다고 생각해요
Strengthen our relationship, just like the relationship between Qin and Jin.
진과 진의 관계처럼 우리의 관계를 강화하십시오 .
He is my big brother!
그는 나의 큰 형이에요!
A sirta. he
시르타. 그
She must be my consort.
그녀는 내 배우자임에 틀림없어요.
♫ Under the sunset♫
♫ 석양 아래♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫나는 수천 마일을 여행했어요♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 달빛 아래서 시타르를 연주해 보세요 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 술은 내가 잊지 못하게 해줄 거예요 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 당신은 조용히 돌아서서 결혼식 장부를 덮습니다♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫나는 너 같은 사람을 기다리며 조용히 시타르를 연주한다 ♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫결국 당신은 나의 피할 수 없는 운명♫